翻译：Iz      Tiogy      红豆包      小布拿拿
校对&总监：Iz
后期：斯人     时间轴：深夏桃子
更多动画  就在@欧美动漫汉化军团
《开心汉堡店》第五季第十六集
"虫"八哥
除虫害公司
真不敢相信我们周六还得来学校
I can't believe we're at school on a Saturday.
今天奇幻码头要举办棉花糖大会呢
The Cotton Candy Festival is today at Wonder Wharf!
听说有很特别的口味
I heard they have unusual and exotic flavors.
-比如千层面口味  -香辣酱口味
- Like lasagna. - And chimichurri!
你们永远不会知道了  因为你们都得留校
Well, you'll never know since you'll all be in detention.
老爸  只要你现在立刻带我们去奇幻码头
Dad, Tina will give you all the money in her bank account
蒂娜就把她银行账户里的钱都给你
if you take us to Wonder Wharf right now.
拜托了  等把我们放出来
Please? By the time we get out of detention,
大会都该结束了
the festival will be over.
你们惹麻烦之前
Well, you should've thought about
就应该想到这点了
that before you got in trouble.
好孩子有棉花糖吃  坏孩子啥都没有
Good kids eat cotton, bad kids eat notton'.
真不敢相信你居然不替我留校
I can't believe you won't go to detention for me.
不是说了吗  如果可以的话我也愿意
I already told you, if I could I would,
但是我穿不进你的衣服  苔米
but I can't fit into your clothes, Tammy.
你知道我很想的
You know I want to.
你是想替我留校
You want to go to detention for me
还是想穿我的衣服
or you want to wear my clothes?
去吧
J-Just go.
老妈  真不敢相信我被留校了
Mom, I can't believe I got detention.
完全不用担心
Don't even worry about it.
你美极了
You're, like, really pretty.
全天  是吧
All day, huh?
这下能好好治治你了
Oof, this is gonna suck for you, really.
是鲍勃  你好贝尔彻
Hey, there's Bob. Hey, Belcher!
你三个孩子都被留校了啊
You got three kids in detention, huh?
没错  吉米
Yeah, Jimmy.
我只有一个  我赢啦
I only got one. I win!
我昨天
Well, I... had none in...
没有孩子被留校
detention yesterday!
你有几个孩子
How many did you have in...
别摇上窗户
Don't roll up your window!
摇下来
Roll it back down!
你们有谁
Well? Do any of you
要为自己解释一下
have anything to say for yourselves
昨天在学校发生了什么吗
after what happened yesterday at school?
我有话要讲
I have something to say.
我想代苔米道歉
I'd like to apologize on behalf of Tammy.
她是个可怕的女人  是她挑起了这一切
She's a horrible person who caused all of this,
除了她  应该把大家
and everyone should be released
都从这地狱里放出去  谢谢
from this hell pit except her. Thank you.
你是个发型糟糕的骗子
You're a liar without a hair dryer.
这都是你姐姐的错
This is your sister's fault!
我是哥哥
I'm a boy!
不是你  吉恩  我说蒂娜
Not you, Gene. Tina.
她导致了这一切的发生
She caused all of this.
如果导致的意思是没有导致  那么我承认
If by "Caused" you mean "Didn't cause," then, yeah,
-我导致了这一切  击掌  -好样的
- I caused this. High five. - Sure.
-好疼  -在我看来
- Too hard. - From what I remember,
这都仅仅是因为一件事引起的  时尚
this was caused by one thing and one thing only: fashion.
开始了
Okay, so this is it.
我新装扮的第一天
Day one with my new look.
真不敢相信我戴了这个来学校
I can't believe I'm wearing this at school.
我都认不出来你了
I barely recognize you.
也许我不应该戴  不  不
Maybe I shouldn't do it. No, no.
要想引人注目  就得酷炫
If you want to dazzle, you got to take razzles.
"酷炫"是"冒险"的一种更酷炫的说法
That's a dazzling way to say "Risks."
时尚手环  时尚冒险
You take fashion risks with your fashion wrists.
你们好吗
Hi, how are you guys?
他们都哑口无言了  蒂娜
They're speechless, Tina.
他们不知道该说些什么
They don't know what to say
因为他们从来没见过这么独特的东西
because they've never seen anything so original.
我想你说得对
I think you're right.
伙计们  这真棒极了
Guys, this is going great.
天呐
Oh, my God!
蒂娜戴了一条和你一样的手环  苔米
Tina's wearing the same bracelet as you, Tammy!
蒂娜  马上摘下来
Tina, you need to take that off right now.
从我昨天买下这星星荧光手环起
Sparkle jelly bracelets are my thing since yesterday
-它就是我专属的了  -没错
- when I bought it. - Yeah.
苔米  我理解你很失望
Tammy, I understand you're disappointed.
我也有点失望
I'm a little disappointed, too.
在我看到你戴之前
Before I saw it on you,
我还觉得这手环很漂亮
I thought this bracelet was classy.
摘  下  它
Take... it... off.
我  宁  可  去  死
I... would... rather... die.
那你就去死吧
Then you will die!
放开我姐姐
Get off my sister!
你们在玩"红色漫游者"吗[一种儿童游戏]
Hey! You guys playing Red Rover?
齐克来啦
Send Zeke on over!
我不知道应该怎么办了
I don't know what to do!
找消防部门吧
The fire department will fix this!
没错  泡沫派对来啦
Yeah! Foam party!
周六  留校
Detention! Saturday!
-所有人  -什么
- All of you! - What?!
承认吧  蒂娜
Admit it, Tina, the only reason
你戴那手环
you wore that sparkle jelly bracelet
就是为了模仿我
was because you wanted to copy me, okay?
才不是  我戴它是因为
That's not true. I wore it because I wanted
我想让它为我代言
to make a statement without saying a word.
那我有话要对你说了
Mm-kay, well, I have a statement for you then.
讨厌
Darn it!
我怎么不能自如的放屁呢
Why can't I fart when I want to?
孩子们呢
Where are the kids?
他们被留校了  泰迪
They got detention, Teddy.
在棉花糖大会这天吗
On the day of the Cotton Candy Festival?
真残忍
That's rough.
真希望我能去  但我怕我控制不住自己
Wish I could go, but I can't trust myself.
你本打算就吃一个  最多两个
You think you're gonna get one, maybe two cottons,
下一秒你就被赶出大会了
next thing you know you're getting kicked out
还被拿走了车钥匙
of the festival, and they take away your car keys.
-好吧  -你好  亲爱的
- Right. - Hi, sweetie.
我能帮你什么吗
Can I help you?
下午好  我叫莎莉
Hi. Good afternoon. My name is Sally.
希望你们今天过得很愉快
I hope that you're enjoying your day.
你们能买些杂志期刊
Would you like to buy some magazine subscriptions
来帮助我锻炼交流技巧
to help me learn communication skills,
帮助我买课本
help me buy textbooks,
送我去佛罗里达的海龟营地旅行吗
and send me on a trip to Turtle Camp in Florida?
这些我只要再积283分就都能实现了
I'm only 283 points away from my goal.
海龟营地
Turtle Camp?
不用了  谢谢
No, thanks.
我们不感兴趣  一点兴趣都没有
We're-we're not interested. At all.
我喜欢海龟
I love turtles.
你在营地干些什么
What do you do at camp?
你和大家在小独木舟里
You get in a little canoe with them?
做海龟手工吗
do turtle crafts?
你们可以从这些当中任意选择十本杂志
You can select up to ten magazines
只需要17美金
from any of these titles for only $17.
-听起来很划算啊  要在哪签字  -假的
- That sounds like a great deal. Where do I sign?  - Fake.
-是假的  不是真的  -我看看
- This is fake. Not real. - I'll take a look!
-假的  -我看看都有什么
- Fake. - Let me see what you got.
《浴缸狂粉》
Jacuzzi Enthusiast.
还有《每月洗液》
Ooh, they got Lotion Monthly.
《健康宝宝文摘》
Healthy Babies Digest.
琳  他们不会给你寄杂志
Lin, th-they never send you the magazines.
你们会在30天内收到杂志
You will start receiving issues within 30 days.
等一下  莎莉
Hold on one second, Sally.
快速和我妻子商量下
Quick conversation over here with my wife.
-琳  不要买  -还有《露趾生活》
- Lin, no. - They have Open-Toe Living.
琳达  这是个骗局
Linda, it's a scam.
你给他们钱  他们就私饱中囊
You give them money, and they just take it.
莎莉是个骗子吗  我们的莎莉
Sally's a scammer? Our Sally?
有人也把她给骗了
Somebody's scamming her, too.
他们指使她做的
They put her up to it.
什么情况
What are we talking about over here?
有人骗了莎莉
Somebody is scamming Sally.
-混蛋  -我们得帮助她
- Bastard! - We got to help her.
或者我们只要友好地请她离开
Or we can just nicely ask her to leave.
不行  鲍鲍  我们今天有三个孩子被留校
No, Bobby. We lost three kids to detention today.
我们不能让莎莉也落得如此下场
We're not losing Sally, too.
-莎莉  -怎么了
- Sally! - What?
-没什么  莎莉  -没啥
- Nothing, Sally! Nothing. - Uh, no.
时尚已经成了瓦格斯塔夫小学的毒瘤
Fashion has become toxic here at Wagstaff.
有人可能不信  我也曾是所谓的
Believe it or not, even I have been the recipient
"时尚涂鸦"的受害者
of what some people call a "Fashion thrashin'."
什么
Wha...
穿什么毛背心  我看是烂背心吧
什么
What?!
什么  "烂背心"
Wh-What? "More like sweater mess"?
那晚我很生气
That night, I was upset.
但我没有怒发冲冠
But instead of lashing out in anger,
我拿起了针
I turned to the needle.
没错  就是针线的针
That's right. The knitting needle.
我用它和时尚和解了
I rehabilitated myself with fashion.
这故事好狗血  福旺德老师
That's an emotional-ass story, Mr. Frond.
时尚应该是一种表达方式
Fashion should be a form of expression,
而不是攻击人的武器
not a weapon to tear people down.
这就是我决定把你们分组
That is why I have decided to team you up
来一场时尚竞赛的原因
and pitch you against each other in a fashion contest.
-我完全听懂了  -不用了谢谢
- So far, this all makes sense. - No, thanks.
如果要找我
If you need me,
我就在这儿无限放空
I'll be zoning out pretty hard over here.
那我睁着眼睡觉就好
And I'm gonna sleep with my eyes open.
像这样
Like this.
好吧  好吧  好吧
Fine. Fine, fine, fine, fine!
获胜的一队
The winning team will be allowed
可以提前三小时离开
to leave detention three hours early.
-什么  -真的吗
- Wait, what? - Seriously?
这样我们就可以去棉花糖大会了
We can go to the Cotton Candy Festival!
福旺德老师  就这么说定了
Mr. Frond, you got yourself a fashion contest.
欢迎来到"恐怖炫彩"时尚竞赛
Welcome to... Scared Fabulous!
蒂娜  我们也来赌一把吧
Hey, Tina. How about a side bet?
赢的人可以继续戴星星荧光手环
Winner gets to wear the sparkle jelly bracelet.
输的得把它扔垃圾桶
Loser has to throw theirs in the trash.
-成交  -像《甜心俏佳人》一样妥妥的赌
- Deal. - We've got a deal like Ally McBeal.
像斯皮尔伯...格一样妥妥的赌
We've got a deal like Steven Spiel... berg.
欢迎来到恐怖炫彩
Welcome to Scared Fabulous.
你们将分队  迎接三个挑战
You will divide into teams and face three challenges.
你们将设计草图  收集材料
You'll sketch designs, collect materials,
并在假人上完成作品
and construct outfits on your CPR dummy.
这还不错  那个假人穿啥都很酷
Good news for us, 'cause that dummy looks hot in anything.
每队其中一人要穿着设计好的服装走T台
Then one of you will walk your design down the runway.
届时将有三位公正
You will have three impartial judges
且有着敏锐时尚感的评委评分
with a keen sense of fashion:
舒娜老师  布莱文斯教练和布兰卡先生
Ms. Schnur, Coach Blevins and Mr. Branca.
什么  三巨头
What? The big three?
他们这周不应该在米兰吗
Aren't they all supposed to be in Milan this week?
除了我  就只有他们三个
They're the only other faculty members
今天还在学校了
who happen to be in the building today.
我加入苔米队
I'm on Tammy's team!
我跟着齐克
I want to be on Zeke's team.
终有一天我们会开启自己的
Someday we're gonna start
男装时尚品牌  然后住在车里
our own men's fashion line then live in a van!
没错  品牌名就叫"酷裤"
Yeah! Called Fancy Pants!
你整个人会像你的裤子一样酷
You're gonna fance the way you pants.
我保证
I guarantee it!
好吧
Fine, then.
最后一组就是贝尔彻了
The last team will be the Belcher kids.
虽然你们有三个人
There are three of you,
不过似乎不是什么优势
but I don't really see that as an advantage.
别小看我们  我们家族的座右铭是
Don't underestimate us. Our family's motto is,
"没准这次会交好运"
"Maybe we'll get lucky this time."
我还以为是  "不许碰那个了
I thought it was, "Stop touching that!
弄得全是油"
You're getting it all greasy!"
莎莉  汉堡怎么样
How's the burger, Sally?
-喜欢吗  -还行  谢谢
- You like it? - It's fine. Thanks.
你们到底买不买杂志呢
So, are you guys gonna buy any magazines?
-不买  因为你的人生是个谎言  -什么
- No, Sally, 'cause your life is a lie. - What?
琳达  莎莉  抱歉
Linda. Sorry, Sally.
我妻子的意思是
What my wife is trying to say is that
没有什么杂志
there are no magazines.
你应该卷入了一场骗局
You're-you're involved in a scam.
有人在利用你
Somebody is using you.
但我还有283分就达到目标了
But I'm only 283 points away from reaching my goal.
莎莉  没有分
Sally! There are no points!
-什么  -没有目标
- What? - There is no goal!
-可...  -没有海龟
- But... - There are no turtles!
你得清醒
You got to get out!
海龟怎么了
What happened to the turtles?
琳达  冷静
Linda, calm down.
我还是先走吧
I guess I'm gonna get going.
好的  不过你听明白
Okay, yeah, but did you get
我们刚才说的话了吗
what we were talking about here?
来抱一下
Give me a quick hug!
我不应该
We'll, I'm not supposed...
-莎莉  -我得走了
- Sally. - I got to be on my way, but,
抱歉  抱...
sorry to, uh... sorry to,
抱歉打扰了
sorry to, uh... sorry to bother you.
-再见  莎莉  -真是个好孩子
- Bye, Sally. - What a nice girl.
等等  我的包呢  我的包
Wait, where's my purse? My purse!
哦在这里  在这儿
Oh, there it is. There it is.
一切正常
Everything's okay.
-我的薯条呢  -被你吃了  泰迪
- My fries! - You ate them, Teddy.
好吧  我能再来点吗
Oh, okay. Can I get another fry over here please?
我刚给斯普尔斯校长的
All right. I just got off the phone
语音信箱留了言
with Principal Spoors' voicemail.
传达得很顺利
I feel like the message went really well,
即将进行的比赛
and I think what we're looking at here
可能是将火遍全美的电视节目的试播集
is a pilot program that will probably go national.
舒娜老师  第一个挑战是什么
So, Ms. Schnur, what is the first challenge?
我的挑战是  每一组将设计一套服装
For my challenge, I want each team to design an outfit
适合我在三天假期里穿的
that I can wear over a three-day holiday weekend.
好吧舒娜  什么样的假期
All right, Schnur, what are we talking here?
武术比赛
Martial arts tournament?
加拿大瘾君子狂奔节  古董收购
Canadian pill run? Antiquing?
不  我会三天都坐在沙发上
No. I'm just gonna sit on the couch all weekend
连续看大卫・修蒙[曾出演老友记]的电影
and watch a David Schwimmer movie marathon.
棒  设计师们
Great! Okay, designers,
改造她也改造你们自己吧
time to make her fab while you rehab.
舒娜老师要在沙发上坐三天
Ms. Schnur wants to sit on the couch for three days.
吉恩  简直是为你量身打造的设计
Gene, you were born to design this outfit.
我可是沙发达人中的
I'm like the Steve Jobs
乔布斯啊
of sitting on the couch for three days.
蒂娜  你可以做模特
Tina, you can be our model.
我不知道
I don't know.
我走路不太擅长
I'm not very good at walking.
你已经有进步了
You're getting better.
只要扬着头
Just keep your head high,
抬起膝盖
pick your knees up,
每一步都重重地踏下就好了
and make every step a glamorous stomp.
你是说  像马那样吗
You mean like a horse?
没错
Yeah.
跑起来吧  姐们
Clip-clop, girl!
行
I'm in.
设计师们  你们每队
All right, designers, you each have
有五分钟的时间收集材料
five minutes to collect your materials.
-我们要去纺织品店吗  -不
- Are we going to the fabric store? - No!
在这次挑战中
For this challenge,
你们只能使用舒娜老师
you can only use materials
材料柜里的材料
from Ms. Schnur's supply closet.
预备  开始
And your time starts... now!
快  快  快
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
蒂娜  你都抄袭了我的手链
you copied my bracelet, Tina,
还要抢我的订书机吗
and now you want to take my stapler?
怎么不把你的嘴订上呢
Why don't you staple your mouth shut,
一直张着
'cause your face keeps falling open
还总冒出些蠢话
and dumb words keep coming out.
我的
Mine!
不
No...!
哦这里还有一个
Oh, there's another one right here.
欢迎来到T台秀
Welcome to the runway.
你们也知道  在时尚界
As you know in fashion,
今天还在圈里
one day you're in,
第二天可能就幡然醒悟
the next day you're rehabilitated.
然后回到自由的世界吃着棉花糖
And out free in the world eating cotton candy
被扔到脸上什么的
to shove it in your face, the whole thing.
本轮获胜者将获得下轮挑战的豁免权
The winner of this challenge will receive immunity
现在开始吧
in the next round. Let's start the show!
小吉穿着沙发套装
J-Ju's wearing the Couch-fit!
总...总有那么几天
For the d... For those days
你就是不想离开沙发
you just don't want to get off the couch,
现在你也不必离开了
now you don't have to.
-因为你就是沙发  -转一下
- 'Cause you are the couch. - Spin.
看起来不错
Looking good, girl!
不论是出门
It doesn't matter if she's out
还是坐在沙发上
on the town or in on the couch,
舒娜老师都应该又美又迷人
we wanted Ms. Schnur to look fun and flirty,
而不是又脏又恶心
not gross and dirty.
就是这样
This is me right now.
嗒嗒嗒
And... clip-clop. Clip-clop.
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
向你们隆重介绍  成人围裙
I introduce to you the Adult Bib.
口袋由铝箔衬里
The pockets are lined with aluminum foil
可为鸡翅保温
to keep your chicken wings warm.
我们赢定了  吉恩  蒂娜的效果很不错
We got this, Gene. Tina looks great out there.
有点像马  不过不错
Horsey but good.
不  我侄子的照片
Oh, no! My nephew through the years!
干得好  蒂娜  祝你在毁了
Oh, nice one, Tina. good luck winning
舒娜老师的家庭后还能获胜
after you ruined Ms. Schnur's family forever.
现在该选择胜者了
Now it's time to pick a winner and see
谁将得到豁免权  直接晋级最后一轮呢
who will get immunity and move directly to the final round.
齐克  小吉米  你们的设计太无礼了
Zeke, Jimmy Jr., I found your look incredibly offensive.
我可不是沙发
I am not a couch.
苔米  乔丝玲
Tammy, Jocelyn,
你们颇具调情意味的服装
your flirty outfit would send the wrong message
会让中餐馆的送餐员误会的
to the Chinese food delivery guy.
他叫恩里克
His name is Enrique,
他本来就已经对我很有意图了
and he's already very forward with me.
贝尔彻家的  你们的模特摔倒
Belcher children, your model fell over
毁了我侄子内森的所有照片
and destroyed all my photographs of Nathan.
舒娜老师  该宣布结果了
Ms. Schnur, it's time to announce your decision.
本次挑战的赢家是...
The winner of this challenge is...
拜托  舒娜
Come on, Schnur.
让我们去那甜得发腻的棉花糖大会吧
Get us to that sweet, sweet cotton candy.
苔米和乔丝玲
...Tammy and Jocelyn.
-我们好受欢迎  -太棒了  太棒了
- Yay! We're popular! - Yes! Yes!
超级嫉妒我吧
Sparkle jealous, much?
吧唧吧唧吧唧  这就是你
Blah, blah, blah much? That's you.
我超级想吃棉花糖  那就是我
I want cotton candy much! That's me!
孩子们  欢迎来到第二轮
Kids, welcome to round two.
布莱文斯教练  跟设计师们
Coach Blevins, tell the designers
说说第二轮挑战的规则
about their next challenge.
我今天来
I just came in today
是想把这些摔跤垫处理掉
to pull up these old wrestling mats
上面全是...血和口水
because they're full of, uh, blood and spit.
另外  我还得扔掉这些毛衫
Also, I need to throw out these jerseys.
它们都太过时了
They're from the '60s,
上面还有很多细菌
and they have high levels of bacteria.
细菌难道不是人们编出来的东西么
Yeah, but isn't bacteria just a myth?
也就是说
So let's just say the materials
本轮挑战的材料就是摔跤垫和旧毛衫
for this challenge will be wrestling mats and old jerseys.
现在跟他们说说你想要什么样的服装
Now, tell them what kind of outfit you want.
下周六
Well, next Saturday,
我上午要参加摔跤大会
I have a wrestling meet in the morning,
下午上交通法规课
traffic school in the afternoon
晚上要去跳莎莎舞
and salsa dancing at night.
所以我需要一件同时满足三个功能的服装
So I guess I need an outfit that's a triple threat:
当教练  拿回我的驾驶证  跳舞
coaching, getting my license back, dancing.
你们都听到了吧
You heard the man.
现在开始吧  设计师们
Let's get started, designers.
祝你们好运  可怜的设计师们
Good luck, designer-whiners!
我们有豁免权啦
We have immunity!
那意味着我们这轮不用设计服装了
That means we don't have to design an outfit this round,
而且永远不会死了
and we can never die.
第一个对了  第二个没那回事
Just the first thing. The second thing is incorrect.
不好意思  嗨
Excuse me. Hi.
有什么可以帮忙的吗
Can I help you?
你们是不是跟这女孩说她被骗了
Did you tell this girl that she was part of a scam?
-说了一点吧  -你是谁
- A little bit? - Who are you?
翠西  过去16年里  我一直致力于
I'm Trish, and I've been helping girls like Sally
帮助莎莉这样的女孩锻炼沟通能力
get communication skills, textbooks
买课本  去弗罗里达旅行
and trips to Florida for the last 16 years.
所以你就是那个策划
Oh, okay. So you're the one
假海龟营地的人咯
behind the whole fake Turtle Camp thing?
假海龟营地
Fake Turtle Camp thing?
你知道这些女孩能从中学到什么吗
Do you know what these girls learn down there?
-学会从她们自己的龟壳里爬出来  -是么
- They learn to come out of their shell. - Yup.
我跟你讲个故事吧
Let me tell you a story, huh?
很久以前  有一个女孩
Once upon a time, there was a little girl.
她一度有点大舌头  像这样
And she used to stutter with a lisp, like this.
后来她通过卖杂志参加了海龟营地
And then she sold magazines and went to Turtle Camp,
她的人生因此改变
and everything changed.
那是你吗
Was it you?
是的  算是吧
Yes. Let's say yes.
这些杂志能改变她们的人生
These magazines change lives.
天呐  鲍鲍  这不是骗局
Oh, my God, Bobby, it's not a scam.
-我们都想错了  -是么
- We had it all wrong. - Uh, yeah.
我还是觉得是胡说八道
Still think this is a bunch of crap.
感觉你就是让这些女孩卖杂志
It-it just seems like you're asking girls
然后把钱据为己有
to sell magazines and then taking the money.
你知道海龟还能做什么吗
Okay, you know what else a turtle can do?
知道吗
Do you know?
小海龟  能做什么
A little turtle, what can it do, hmm?
-能扇人  -扇人的海龟
- It can snap! - Snapping turtles!
所以你们是想看我扇人呢
So do you want to see me snap, hmm?
-不要  -还是买我的杂志
- No. - Or do you want to buy some magazines?
冷静  你在做什么
Calm down. What are you doing?
行了  行了  别激动
Okay, okay, take it easy.
鲍鲍  她要把柜台掀翻了
Oh, no! Bobby, she's pulling up the counter!
你们  要不要  买杂志
Do... you... want to buy any... magazines?!
快说买  鲍勃  快说买
Say yes, Bobby! Say yes!
老天  我要抓狂了
God, I'm going crazy!
好吧  你有关于做菜的杂志吗
Okay, do you have any magazines about cooking?
我们有《厨房菜谱》
We have Cooking in the Kitchen.
那好  我去那支票簿
Great. I'll get my checkbook.
快去拿
Get your checkbook.
-快去  -我在去了
- Get it! - I'm getting it!
-快点  -我找不到了
- Hurry! - I can't find it!
好了  本轮设计结束了
Okay, the designs are complete.
该让他们承受枪林弹雨的批评了
Let's tear them apart metaphorically.
布莱文斯教练穿着这套全天适用服装
Coach Blevins will be sporty and spicy
将会又运动又性感
in this one-piece, all-day dress shirt.
你们会发现这套是露背装
You'll notice the design is backless,
专为莎莎舞设计
which is perfect for salsa dancing
并有利于你拿回驾驶证
and gettinyour license back.
-来啊  -齐克现在穿的是
- Come on! - Zeke is wearing
传统日本武士服
a traditional Japanese samurai outfit.
这套服装在哪儿都能完美融入
'Cause there is nowhere this outfit doesn't fit in
并让你熠熠闪光
and stand out.
布莱文斯教练  该宣布
Coach Blevins, it's time
这次挑战的赢家了
to announce the winner of this challenge
他们将在最后一轮中迎战乔丝玲和苔米
and who will face Tammy and Jocelyn in the final round!
我对时尚一窍不通
I honestly don't know anything about fashion.
可以是平局吗
Can we just call it a tie?
不行  不能是平局
No, we cannot call it a tie.
这是时尚  必须得有赢家
It's fashion. There has to be a winner
和输家  选吧
and a loser. Pick one!
要不
Maybe
让他们摔跤决定吧
they should just wrestle for it.
我的体育课上都是用这种方式来决胜负的
That's how I usually settle things in my gym class.
好吧  如果你非要这样
Fine, then. If that's what it takes
才能选出获胜者
for you to pick a winner,
那就让他们摔跤吧
then we'll have them wrestle.
等等  啥
Wait. What?
开始
Go!
好耶  这就是我眼中的时装秀
Yeah! This is my kind of fashion show!
吉恩  快来迎战  我要打败你
Gene, get over here! I'm gonna get ya!
-来啊  来啊  -我的衣服刚熨过
- Come on! Come on! - I just ironed this outfit!
斯普尔斯校长
Oh, hello, Principal Spoors.
我们正在举行时尚比赛
We're right in the middle of a fashion show.
你打来是问这个的吧
I assume you're calling about that?
我  我有点听不清你讲什么
It's-it's a little hard to hear you.
-你  你说啥  -住手
- Wh-What were you saying? - Stop it!
你...你说你怎么恐怖炫彩来着
Oh, you... you what Scared Fabulous?
你讨厌  好吧
You hate it. Okay.
你  是在说反话吗
Like, ironically?
蒂娜  你们输定了
Hey, Tina! You guys are gonna lose!
我是说  准备好
So bracelet in your facelet is
把你的手环扔自己脸上吧
what I'm talking about!
要来一局吗  苔米
You want to go, Tammy?
-要来一局吗  -来呀
- Want to go?! - Yeah!
我还想再和你谈谈  再谈谈
I'd like to talk to you more, a little more,
关于...好吧
about the... Oh. Okay, right.
周末不要再给你打电话了
No more calls on the weekend.
明白  再见
Got it. Right. Bye.
设计师们  我刚和校长通了电话
So, designers, I just spoke with Principal Spoors,
情况有变
and there have been some new developments.
恐怖炫彩时装比赛临时终止
Scared Fabulous will abruptly end now,
你们要回教室
and we'll all be returning to class
继续留校了
where detention will resume as usual.
啥
What?!
决赛呢
What about the finals?
棉花糖大会呢
And the Cotton Candy Festival!
福旺德老师  等等
Mr. Frond, hold on.
你就这样让斯普尔斯校长
You're gonna let Principal Spoors
毙掉你的改造计划吗
just shut down our rehabilitation?
这是我俩商议后的决定
It was a mutual decision.
我知道是怎么一回事
Oh, I get what's going on.
他觉得你没资格策划
He didn't think you were qualified
时尚拯救问题青年项目
to run a fashion-based at-risk youth program.
也许得找其它老师
Maybe another teacher will have to do it.
有时尚品味的老师
Someone with, say, a knack for fashion.
我...我可是瓦格斯塔夫的潮男
I... I'm Wagstaff's fashion guy.
我的设计才华比你们所有人加起来还多
I'm a better designer than all of you combined.
我都能把你缝在桌子底下
I could sew you under the table.
是么
Oh, really?
那你怎么不用针线
Well, why don't you put your knitting needles
缝缝你的嘴呢
where your mouth is?
最后一轮挑战
One last challenge...
我们所有人和你对决
all of us against you.
布兰卡当评委  可以吗  布兰卡先生
Mr. Branca judges. Right, Mr. Branca?
我喜欢简洁的线条和轮廓
I like clean lines and simple silhouettes.
不要  我不要和蒂娜一组  办不到
No. I don't want to work with Tina. I won't do it.
闭嘴苔米  我是想把我们大家都弄出去
Tammy shush. I'm getting us out of here.
我不要和蒂娜一组
I don't want to work with Tina.
-我不...我  -闭嘴  闭嘴
- I don't... I... - Stop it! Just shush. Shush!
如果你赢了  我们就告诉斯普尔斯校长
If you win, we'll tell Principal Spoors
你完全把我们给镇住了
that you scared us fabulous,
你是我们见过最会穿衣服的人
and that you're the best dressed man we've ever seen.
但如果我们赢了  就让我们都提前离开
But if we win, we all get to leave early.
我是个针线高手  不是退缩小丑
I'm a knitter, not a quitter.
孩子们  赌一把吧
Kids, you're on.
-太好了  -欧耶
- All right! - Hell yeah!
天呐  来吧  赌一把
Oh, my God, yeah! Let's do it.
你可以霸占我们的周六上午
You can take our Saturday morning,
但愿永远别让你夺走
but you'll hopefully never take away
我们的周六下午中后半段
our mid-to-late Saturday afternoon!
终极对决即将展开
Let the ultimate challenge begin.
潮爆老师对战留校学生
The fashionista versus the detentionistas.
真不敢相信我要和蒂娜一队
I can't believe I have to work with Tina.
她浑身散发一股要输的气场
She smells like failure,
还一头番茄酱味儿
and her hair smells like ketchup.
你以为我想和你一队么  苔米
It's not like I want to work with you, either, Tammy.
还有  你说错了
And you're wrong.
我头发没有番茄酱味儿  皮肤才有
My hair doesn't smell like ketchup. My skin does.
各位  为了终极对决
Oh. You guys, try to keep it together
咱能团结点吗
for one last challenge.
等我们都出去了
We'll all get out of here,
你们可以在外面打一架
and you can hate each other on the outside.
我来描述下背景
Let me paint a picture.
我是一个故国的总统
I am president in the old country.
革命正在打响
The revolution is underway.
反叛军已经攻入我的宫殿
The rebels have charged into my palace,
把我拉到大街上
dragged me onto the street,
要求公正的处决
and are demanding justice.
现在我必须要发表一番演说
I must give a speech.
你们要给我设计一套能改变我人生的衣服
I want you to design a look
材料就用我如今在你们这
that will save my life using a material
伟大的国家工作时每天都会接触到的东西
that I now work with every day in your wonderful country.
也就是垃圾  限时20分钟  开挖吧
Trash. You have 20 minutes. Dig!
快上  快上
Let's go! Let's go!
要付你多少钱
So what do we owe you?
就算160块吧
Let's call it $160.
那可不是杂志的价钱
That's not how much magazines cost.
嘿  鲍勃
Hey, Bob.
我就是来确认下
Just wanted to check how many kids
你今天得从学校接几个被留校的娃回来
you were gonna be picking up from detention.
-还是三个吗  -现在没心情  吉米
- Still three? - Not now, Jimmy.
我正忙着呢
We're in the middle of something here.
是么  你在说啥呢
Yeah? What are you talking about?
你们在做什么
What are you doing?
知道吗  就是...
You know what? Just...
算了  你  你不会感兴趣的
Nah, you-you wouldn't be interested.
那倒是
Ha! Yeah, you're right.
但你可以先告诉我  然后我再表示不感兴趣
But, uh, you know, tell me so I can not be interested.
我们打算拨出我们店盈利的一部分
Well, we were just using some of our profits
帮助这位莎莉小朋友买书
to help Sally here with her textbooks
提高沟通技能  并送她参加海龟营地
and communication skills and Turtle Camp.
做点慈善
Just some philanthropy.
回报社会
You know, giving back to the community.
我们订了20本杂志
We bought 20 magazine subscriptions,
但没啥大不了的
but it's not a big deal.
你不会感兴趣的
Nothing you'd be interested in.
20本  弱爆了  我能买40本
20? That's dumb. I could buy 40.
我不信
I don't think you could.
我可以  易如反掌
Oh, yeah, I could easily.
我可爱回报社会了
I give back like a son of a bitch.
等你们这边弄完
Hey, uh, why don't you guys come over
就到我的店里来吧
to my place after you're done here?
我每种杂志都订两本
I'll take two of everything.
好的  先生  我们马上就来
Yes, sir! You got it.
你们会在12到18周以内
You should receive your first issues
收到你们的第一期杂志
in ten to 12 to 18 weeks, huh?
谢谢你们的支持  再见
Okay, thanks for your support. Bye!
我会从海龟营地给你们寄明信片的
And I'll send you a postcard from Turtle Camp.
但愿你会  莎莉
I hope you do, Sally.
真心希望
I really hope you do.
我也是  我也希望自己会
Me, too. I hope I do it, too.
拜  爱你哦  莎莉
Bye. Love you, Sally!
好吧  谢...谢谢
Okay, thank-thank you.
今天真是个好日子
Today was a good day.
是啊  我们被整了  但吉米被整得更惨
Yeah. We got screwed, but Jimmy got screwed more.
没错
Yeah.
我找到几根黄瓜
I found some cucumber.
也许我们能用它做个黄瓜背心
Maybe we can make a cucumber-bund?
快找啊  菲利普
Come on, Philip.
是向世界证明你实力的时候了
It's time to prove yourself to the world.
做出超级福旺德的东西吧
Let's make something Fronderful!
我们的花生酱不够了
We're out of peanut butter!
这下上哪儿去找
Where are we gonna find something
能裹在人手腕上的东西
that can wrap around a human wrist? Hey.
让蒂娜和苔米贡献出她们的手环怎么样
What if Tina and Tammy each threw away their bracelets?
可以用来固定生菜
Then we could use them to hold up the lettuce.
-好主意  小吉  -谢谢  齐克
- Great idea J-Ju! - Thanks, Zeke!
没门  我绝不会把我的星星荧光手环脱下来
No way. My sparkle jelly stays on my wrist until I die,
死也不会  死后也不会
and then probably even after that.
蒂娜可以把她的贡献出来
Tina can throw hers away.
把你贡献出来如何
Why don't we throw Tammy away?
别这样  姑娘们
Come on, girls!
能配合点不
Work together for God's sake!
各位  这样我们输定了
Guys, we're gonna lose!
我们这会儿本该在棉花糖大会上的
We're supposed to be at the Cotton Candy Festival right now,
但现在却站在这堆垃圾里
and instead we're standing in a freaking Dumpster!
那就是个蠢荧光手环
They're just stupid sparkle jelly bracelets!
它才不蠢  这是橡胶做的
They're not stupid! They're made of rubber,
有着迷人的魅力
and they have a little charm on them,
能为你代言
and they define who you are.
我去  突然觉得它好蠢
Oh, my God, they are stupid.
我不需要这荧光棒也能发光发亮
I don't need this sparkle jelly to dazzle.
我自己就能发光发亮  我们都能
I dazzle on my own. We all do.
除了苔米
Except for Tammy.
我们怎么能确定这是花生酱
How sure are we that this is peanut butter?
我突然感觉好烧啊
'Cause it's starting to burn.
抱歉打断你们了
Sorry to interrupt.
你们继续吧
Go on with what you were saying.
是这手环把我们带到这儿来的
Tammy, these bracelets are what got us in here.
我们也让它带我们出去吧
Let's use them to get us out of here.
我要把我的扔了
I'm throwing mine away.
谢了  小蒂
Thanks, T.
苔米  把你的也扔了
Tammy, now you throw away your bracelet.
我们要用它来固定另一只胳膊
We need it to hold up the other arm.
你觉得呢  苔米
What do you say, Tammy?
时装秀现在开始
Let the fashion show begin!
这  就是我的设计
This is my design.
是修身款欧式外套
It is a slim-fitted European-style suit.
食堂大妈希尔蒂显然
Apparently, Hildy the lunch lady
在停车场理了发
cuts her hair in the parking lot,
我用她剪下来的头发做了个毛领
which I have used to make a fur lapel.
这是我们用不那么新的生菜做出的最新设计
This is our fresh new design made of not-so-fresh lettuce.
是一套女士西装  专为夏日婚礼
It's a tailored suit, perfect for a summertime wedding,
或者夏日革命设计
or a summertime revolution.
设计师们  我感到很震撼
Designers, I am impressed.
两队都做出了很棒的垃圾设计
Both teams did an excellent job making my trash suit.
福旺德先生  你的服装又时髦又有格调
Mr. Frond, your outfit had class and sass.
孩子们  你们为我设计的生菜西服
Kids, the tailored fit around the wrists
手腕部位简直无懈可击
of my lettuce suit was impeccable!
如果你想的话  我们可以立马让它有懈可击
We can easily change it to peccable if you prefer.
但胜负显而易见
But there was a clear winner.
孩子们
The kids!
什么
What?!
布兰卡先生  你肯定搞错了
Mr. Branca, there must be some mistake.
等下  蒂娜和苔米
Wait. Did Tina and Tammy
把手环贡献出来给你固定袖子了吗
give up their bracelets to secure your sleeves?
你们难道是  齐心合力
Did you... collaborate on fashion
建筑了一座通往友谊和理解的桥么
and build a bridge to friendship and understanding?
是的  福旺德老师
We sure did, Mr. Frond.
-撒手  苔米  -不不  永远别想
- Let it go, Tammy! - No! Never! Never! Never!
我不介意把你整只手臂一起卸下来
I'll take your arm off with it if I have to!
看来我还是成功改造了你们
Maybe I did rehabilitate you kids after all.
也许吧
Yeah, maybe.
好久不见  外面的世界
I missed you, outside world!
现在是哪一年啊
What year is it?!
向糖果大会前进
To the candy!
棉花做的糖果
It's made of cotton!
天呐  斯普尔斯校长来了
Oh, my God. It's Principal Spoors.
学生都走了
All the kids are gone.
天呐  起火啦  起火啦
Oh, my God. Fire! Fire!
*你不喜欢棉花糖吗*
*Don't you love cotton candy? *
*是棉花做的但也是糖*
*It's made of cotton and also candy*
*如果你手指变得黏糊糊*
*If your fingers get sticky*
*那就舔舔你的手指*
*Eat off your hand, lickety-licky *
*你不喜欢棉花糖吗*
*Don't you love cotton candy? *
*不喜欢么  不喜欢么*
*Ah, don't, don't, don't, don't *
*你不喜欢棉花糖吗*
*Don't you love cotton candy? *